Good Morning, brethren!
Emmanuel! Emmanuel! I am Nosakhare Ogiebor Okunbor.
I am a businessman and a politician.
I am a Nigerian based in Benin.
The person by my side is my younger brother ,
I am an independent marketer of liquefied petroleum gas,
popularly called cooking gas.
It all happened on the 20th of February this year.
I hired a truck.
It was loaded with 35 thousand litres of LPG, cooking gas - that is 20 metric tons.
The truck left Lagos for Benin and arrived to Benin at about 10pm.
They called me and said that the truck must be discharged that night.
I said it is not possible to discharge LPG that night.
Moreover my workers and the technical officers
they've all gone home,
that it will be discharged in the morning.
Let me explain this: at one o'clock in the morning one of my trucks has went to Enugu
for upgrade of the safety valve - it almost got burnt on his way to Benin.
The driver called me at about six minutes after one o'clock
to say that my truck caught fire, that they were able to put it down.
Five hours later at about six o'clock
when I woke up
I called one of my managers: "Where are you?"
He said he was at the gate of my gas plant.
I said: "Please, if you are discharging be very careful,
considering what happened about five hours ago."
I left my apartment, I came out.
Within 10 minutes I received a call, distress call: "Gas everywhere!"
I said: "What is happening?"
Before I knew what was happening, the call went off.
Another one came again: "Gas!" This time they said: "Fire!"
I said: "My God!" I screamed. My wife, my children, everybody came out.
I ran into my bedroom and collected my Morning Water and came out.
I faced the direction of my gas plant...
I said: "Son of God, manifest Yourself and destroy the work of devil."
My children ran...
So right there in your house you ministered the Morning Water
in the direction of your gas plant?
I ministered the Morning Water
towards the direction of my gas plant!
Then my children came out, ran into one vehicle.
May God be praised, my His Name be blessed!
My daughter's marriage introduction was to be the next day,
that is on the 21st.
My birthday was on the 22nd.
And this thing happened on the 20th.
So we ran into the vehicle, two of us went towards the fire brigade,
and I went in the direction of my gas plant,
which is about some kilometres away from my house.
When I got to UniBank gate...Those people who know Benin very well...
When I got to UniBank gate, I called some of my workers,
and they said that no fire shed
but the whole area was charged with gas.
I run down and on getting to the place -
vehicles were still passing,
even in the thick of gas - vehicles were still passing.
Which is dangerous. LPG is highly flammable.
So we tried to stop vehicles. It's a very busy road - Benin-Lagos express way.
We succeeded in stopping the vehicles
before police, road safety, soldiers from supply and transport at division -
it is about three kilometres away from a plant.
They came and helped us to stop the vehicles.
No vehicle this time. We are moving.
Sorry sir, when you arrived at the gas plant,
can you describe the scene that you saw? What did you see at that point?
Praise Master Jesus!
The place was charged! Here on the board.
I took this picture after about two hours
from this electric pole to the last fence...
It is about 500 fit from Benin-Lagos express way.
The whole compound was charged with gas.
What you are seeing here is not snow. This is gas, cooking gas.
So the roads - they were all charged.
And when gas escaped... Because it is the vapor goes further than the gas itself
and the vapor is the most dangerous. It can pick fire from anywhere.
But nothing happened!
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Now, sir, we know that you are working in this industry
but for the benefit of those of us present here and viewers all over the world.
We want to understand that the seriousness of this situation -
if not for divine intervention -
if such a situation occurred what would have happened?
If not for the God of TB Joshua - the disaster is unimaginable...
5 kg of cylinders can bring down a building, talkless of 35 000 liters.
That is 20 metric tons that is worse than a bomb.
It can "pfff..." the whole area. What happened in there, would have been a child's play.
It would have been more than about three hundred people that would have died that morning
because close by we have a school and houses around that area.
Millions of naira - if not billions - would have been lost.
Within my compound, within my gas plant I have about three new trucks.
A gas tank is covered so that can take three hundred thousand liters...
That is about 169 metric tons.
Wow! So what you're trying to say, sir, is that in any other situation
any little thing would have sparked a fire in that situation
which would have led to hundreds of lives being lost
and property worth billions being destroyed?
You're right. Even shoe nail can spark fire and that will be end of the investment
and so many people would have been killed and houses burnt down.
Wow, people of God, let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time!
This is indeed a mother of miracles.
And, sir, in your testimony you referenced a similar incident
that happened earlier that you talked about.
I mean just for people to understand how serious this was -
what actually happened in that case compared to
what would have happened in your own?
My explanation is that I am an Emmanuel TV partner.
Every morning I use Morning Water in my company.
Everywhere you have the sticker, every spiritual material from this great church...
Synagogue Church Of All Nations... I have it all around my compound!
It is the handwork of God Almighty.
If not - the story would have been different.
Nothing, no single pin got burnt in my plant.
The only thing lost was the liquid.
Well, let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
And what you're saying, sir, is similar incidents
that happened in the past with other companies or gas plants -
not even to the volume of the gas that actually escaped in your own case -
what will happen in those cases?
A certain newspaper report said that more than hundred people died.
It is not even up to the leakage from that place,
it's not up to thirty percent of what happened in my plant.
Well, so we can really see what Jesus Christ has done in the life of our father here
through ministering the Morning Water,
how God rescued the lives of hundreds,
and what would have been such a serious explosion that would have happened
as a result of this gas leakage.
So can you just explain the other pictures that we're seeing on the board here,
apart from the one you explained earlier.
This is the hired truck. This is the discharge hose.
When you want to discharge, you tie a flexible hose to the truck
and tie the other end to the tank.
When the driver of this hired truck tied off the flange,
he used just two nuts.
You can see from this place - just small.
He supposed to use a long long one but he didn't.
As he opened the valve because of the pressure the one of the nuts gave way.
And this is the curb, you can see it from here,
where one of the nuts gave way.
This is the opening valve.
This is where the gas escaped from.
This is the truck that brought the gas to my plant.
This is from the distance I took the picture - what you are seeing here is not snow,
this is LPG, cooking gas. This is another picture.
These are houses around, the place is now fully developed.
These are houses around my company.
Well, one more time let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
We can only imagine the destruction that would have occurred,
if not for God's divine intervention.
And we thank God for this wonderful wonderful testimony.
So, sir, the light of what Jesus Christ has done -
what is your advice to viewers all over the world?
My advice is: only believe!
It is stated in John 11 that - believe and you will see the glory of God.
I want to say too that the teaching of my mentor, senior prophet TB Joshua,
came in to me, when this incident happened.
At the beginning of the year he said: "Don't take offence".
And several times he has dwelled on that issue.
This truck that brought this gas - immediately it happened
and God saved me, washed me clean of all my iniquities and casted away my sins.
People were begging, calls from all over -
because I'm the deputy national president of all LPG marketers.
Pressures were coming that
the truck - they will pay, they will pay half, they made some different propositions.
Initially they said 20-30.
After about three days I said: "If God could forgive me and protect my property,
what millions of naira?" I went into what man of God preached
and what he stated in Matthew 18 about a king and a servant.
After three days I asked the truck driver to go without pain, cargo.
I allowed him to go.
For the company I've made a proposal that they will pay me about fifty percent of the money,
I asked them to forget about it.
God Almighty saved me, saved my company,
for that reason I have equally to forgive others too.
Well, let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
We thank God, and finally they just give us a word of advice
about this Morning Water that you are holding and the Good Morning sticker -
the instruments that God really used in this situation.
What I have here - Morning Water, Good Morning Sticker -
in fact, any spiritual material from the Synagogue, Church Of All Nations -
is an atomic bomb that destroys the work of satan.
Brethren, don't play with it. Always go with your Morning Water, your Good Morning Sticker.
When you are with it - you are secured, your life is protected,
blessing, breakthrough will be your portion, in Jesus name.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time!
We thank God Almighty for this wonderful wonderful testimony,
the divine protection that this entire gas plant received -
not just our brother and his company but even all the surrounding neighborhood
that would have been affected seriously if this incident had resulted in a fire and explosion.
We give glory to God and right now we'd like to hear a quick word from your brother as well,
who we believe was a witness to this miracle.
So, sir, if you can just introduce yourself to us and just tell us,
what can you say on your own side about this incredible testimony
that your brother has just shared.
Emmanuel! Good Morning, church! My name is Fred Ogiebor Okunbor.
It's my father and my brother.
So on this day, 28 of February we were at home.
We don't live in the same house. So he gave us a call that the gas plant is on fire.
So we didn't know... It was very very bad news.
So we ran out, drove down there.
God is so good. Almost getting there, the road was already blocked
because we live little bit far from the gas plant.
We now walked down there.
Only to get there to discover that the place was in a very messy situation.
God is so good. There was no fire. It would have been a different ball game entirely.
Lives!
It wasn't the property, the company - it was o'k.
But the community would have been raised down, it would be totally raised down.
I've never seen miracle like that. Actually I've never seen the miracle like that.
Sometimes, when I hear about miracle I just say: "It's a normal thing.
God has created us, He will do this thing for us."
But when I saw this thing, when I saw the gas -
my God, you need to see it and you need to see the real work of God -
not the one we talk about. Because you need to experience the work of God
before you know that God exists.
And your brother was saying that the slightest thing
could have caused the fire to spark.
A shoe sole... Some people work and they drag their legs.
It could spark off and the place would have been raised down.
Or even somebody that was a smoker in the enviroment.
There was a smoker. If he was a lunatic, I don't know.
He saw people running helter scelter but he was still smoking.
And with my immediate senior brother - he is not here today -
we ran to the neighboring houses to beg them not to use their stoves, to stop their cooking.
And there was a woman who was already cooking outside with the kids around.
We begged her, we even used water to quench the fire and the pot of soup.
So it was very miraculous. God is good, God is too good.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
So we can understand what our brother is saying -
even at that scene, someone was smoking outside, a woman was cooking -
and ordinarily that alone would have sparked the flammable gas
to have an explosion of fire that would have consumed the entire community.
But because of the Morning Water that had been ministered
and also the Morning Stickers that were in the entire environment -
that's how God secured that environment.
That even the person smoked and the person was cooking - it did not spark the fire.
One more time let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
So as a witness to this miracle what is also your advise, your encouragement
to viewers all over the world?
Just to hang on God, just to keep very very close to God.
My advice is: keep your Morning Water very close to you.
Have it in your pocket, have you Sticker around you
because in the company, like my daddy said earlier, we have the stickers all around -
in the trucks, the private, everywhere.
God is really good and my advice is: get closer to God.
If you have not - get closer. The prophet is just too big. Thank you.
Thank you, Jesus Christ.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus one more time!